Belén Rais

Del Barco Centenera 548 Buenos Aires, Argentina.

M +54 11 66131989

belen.brf@gmail.com

<u>Portfolio</u> https://www.behance.net/bluga



SUMMARY

I am a web developer and designer, graduated in Argentina, with 4+ years of experience in developing and designing a wide range of websites using Wordpress, PHP, HTML, jQuery, JavaScript, MySQL, Photoshop, Illustrator, etc.

I am a results-oriented professional, my goal is to create web developments and designs with the user in mind, creating sites with a useable and intuitive user interface in order to maximize his experience.

I believe that a keen sense of organization and attention to detail are essential qualities to arrive good results.

I have worked on a couple of software companies and also as a freelancer. I helped to develop & design several successful web projects, that are already live online.

I stay always reachable to my clients, in order to give them daily or milestone updates; to make sure that they are satisfied and happy with the quality of my work.

What can you expect from me?

- Honesty
- Hard Work
- Commitment
- Optimism
- Perfectionism
- Passion

EDUCATION

Universidad de Palermo Audiovisual designer 2007-2012

Studied for 5 years and obtained a Bachelor's degree in Audiovisual Design oriented to Web Development. I've enrolled on a studies program that covered developing websites, visual effects, animation and multimedia design.

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer, Virtual Networks Studios

Buenos Aires, Argentina — 2012-Actually

I have participated as a lead developer and designer in several commercial projects, so I have plenty of experience working with WordPress, Joomla, PHP, HTML5, CSS3, jQuery, JavaScript, MySql and also as a Social Media Manager.

Freelance Audiovisual Designer - Web Developer

Buenos Aires, Argentina — 2010-Actually

More than 5 years' experience creating web sites, with particular expertise in Wordpress CMS and front-end development technologies (HTML5, CSS3, JS). // www.bluga.com.ar

Web Solutions Manage, Liderlogo

Buenos Aires, Argentina — 2011-2012

SKILLS

- + HTML5
- + CSS3
- + Wordpress
- + PHP
- + Adobe Illustrator
- + Adobe Photoshop
- + Joomla
- + Responsive
- + SEO